Fukokka?
ふこっか
Yeah.
うん
Why did you go?
なんで行っちゃったの?
some time ago.
さっき
picture?
え?
Did you go first?
先に行っちゃったの?
It felt so good.
気持ちよすぎた
Are you okay after this?
この後平気?
picture?
え?
Are you okay after this?
この後平気?
what?
なに?
Are you okay after this?
この後平気?
What after this?
なにこの後?
Why don't you?
なんでしないの?
Yeah.
うん
do you want to?
したいの?
Yeah.
うん
Don't you even go to Seira?
せいらまでしないの?
I want to.
したい
show me.
見 せて
Come on, let me lick it a lot.
さあ、 いっぱい舐めてもらおう
I'll lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐めてやる
It closes really well.
すごい閉まるね
amazing.
すごい
Is it closed?
閉めてる?
It's not closed.
閉めてない
It's tough.
きついね
It's really closed though.
すごい閉まってるけど
Was it like this?
こんな 感じだったっけ?
Did a lot come out?
いっぱい出てきた?
Why are you so naughty?
なんでこのエッチになってるの?
I'm licking it.
舐めてるよ
Because you're licking me?
舐めてるから?
How did you touch it yourself?
自分でさ、 どんな感じで触ってたの?
Lick it?
舐んで?
Try it.
やってみてよ
Can you help me?
手 伝わるの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
Yeah.
うん
I'm having morning sickness.
つわるんだ
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
I can't help it, so we have a great vision together.
我慢できないから、 すごいビジョン一緒にしてる
Please move.
動いてくれ
Does it move?
動くの?
Give me a hand.
手ついてくれ
At the back.
後ろに
Please move.
動いてくれ
It hurt.
痛った
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Is it in?
入ってる?
It's in.
入ってるよ
you?
お前?
can you move
お前が動けるか
too.
も
Lick it.
舐 めて
舐めて
amazing.
すごい
Lick it.
舐めてよ
Lick it?
舐めて?